Are you addicted to computer games?
你对电脑游戏上瘾吗？
Do you stay up all night playing them?
你会熬夜通宵玩游戏吗？
There's no doubt that the excitement and sophistication of games these days makes them hard to put down.
毫无疑问，当今游戏的刺激和精妙之处让它们令人难以放下。
But should we worry about their effects on our health?
但我们是否应该担心它们对我们健康的影响呢？
We are spoilt for choice when it comes to gaming: You can role play - creating your own fantasy characters and stories, giving you a chance to step out of everyday life into an imaginary world.
说到玩游戏，我们有太多的选择：你可以进行角色扮演——创造你自己的幻想角色和故事，让你有机会走出日常生活，进入一个想象的世界。
And there are shooting games where you can let out your anger and frustration in violent situations where you kill people with guns.
还有射击游戏，在这些游戏中，你可以在使用枪支杀人的暴力场景中释放你的愤怒和沮丧情绪。
Can these kinds of games really be fun and can being absorbed in virtual reality be good for us?
这类游戏真的能带来乐趣吗？沉浸在虚拟现实中对我们有好处吗？
Popular games like Grand Theft Auto have been blamed for everything from falling results at school to provoking acts of extreme violence.
像《侠盗猎车手》这样的热门游戏，被指责应对从学习成绩下降到引发极端暴力行为等各种问题负责。
Internet safety advisor, Alan MacKenzie, thinks "many people understandably will just think that a game is just a game and not realising the explicit content that's in there".
互联网安全顾问艾伦·麦肯齐认为，“很多人理所当然地会认为游戏只是游戏，却没有意识到其中赤裸裸的内容。”
He gives an example of the violence and sexualisation of women which he says is "wholly inappropriate for anybody, never mind children."
他举了一个关于暴力和女性性感化的例子，他说这些内容“对任何人来说都是完全不合适的，更不用说孩子了”。
Others will argue that gaming is a harmless form of entertainment.
其他人会争辩说，玩游戏是一种无害的娱乐形式。
There is evidence that playing video games could actually be good for us.
有证据表明，玩电子游戏实际上可能对我们有好处。
Some games are educational and using game consoles can help children learn good dexterity.
一些游戏具有教育意义，使用游戏主机可以帮助孩子们培养良好的灵活性。
Studies have also shown that the skills used in playing games can cause growth in certain areas of the brain, the ability to think in 3D and even improve our eyesight.
研究还表明，玩游戏所运用的技能可以促进大脑某些区域的发育，提高三维思考能力，甚至改善我们的视力。
Video gamers are also no longer just solitary creatures.
电子游戏玩家也不再只是孤独的个体。
For some, gaming is having a positive effect on their social lives with games like Halo and World of Warcraft often being played in groups.
对一些人来说，像《光环》和《魔兽世界》这样的游戏经常是多人一起玩，这对他们的社交生活产生了积极的影响。
When your group works together to win the game, your sense of achievement is higher than when winning by yourself.
当你的团队一起合作去赢得游戏时，你的成就感会比你独自获胜时更高。
So it seems today, gaming isn't just for geeks and if used in moderation we can all take part.
所以如今看来，玩游戏并不只是怪咖们的专利，如果适度地玩游戏，我们都可以参与其中。
What video games do you play and how do they make you feel?
你玩什么电子游戏，它们让你有怎样的感受呢？